

MOBILE DEVELOPER · WEB DEVELOPE

□ (+254) 700099026 | ■ leviopunga@gmail.com | □ Levi-Opunga | □ levi-baraka

"The best way to predict the future is to invent it"

Summary

I'm a Computer Science grad student specializing in the back-end development and Android. As you can guess I'm a super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Skills

Back-end SpringBoot, Spark,TRPC, REST API

MobileJava and Kotlin Android , React Native (learning)Front-endNextJs, React, Tailwind, Bootstrap, Angular, SolidJsProgrammingJAVA, Kotlin , SQL , Ocaml, Typescript, ShellScript, C/C++

Collaboration Git, Agile and Scrum methods, Notion

Other Competencies LaTeX,Docker, Linux,VmWare,Vitrualbox,FireBase

Spoken Languages English, Swahili

Education

MMU(Multimedia University of Kenya)

Nairobi, Kenya

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Sept. 2021 - Present

Ongiong

Moringa School Nairobi, Kenya

MORINGA SCHOOL CERTIFICATE IN SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT FOR ANDROID AND ANGULAR

2021-2022

- Started in 2021 took a break to join campus and finished during long holiday in August 2022
- · Cerificate Link

UHS(Upperhill School)

Nairobi, Kenya

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA(KCSE)

2017 - 2021

- Delay of one year due to effects of the Covid-19 pandemic
- · Attained an overall grade of A-

Projects

CLOSET APP

Java Android, Firebase, Retrofit

APP

2022

- · An application to get inspiration for outfits and save the ones you like on firebase
- · To be intergated with revery ai which an api that allows for generation of outfits using input images for better user experience
- · Github Link

The Watchlist Java Android, Firebase, Retrofit

Арр

2022

An application using the New York Times api to provide movie reviews and summary. Allows users to leave comments on review and save
movies to their list

• Github Link

Contacts Management Site

SpringBoot,Postgresql,React

,NextJS

Website 2022

A site to demonstrate basic CRUD and Database AUTH functionaly using a springboot backend and nextjs frontend. It utilises spring data jdbc
and hikari pooling for database connectivity

• Frontend : Github Link

· Backend: Github Link

News Api Java Spark ,Postgresql

API 2022

· An api implementing crud operations for a company with staff, news, and departments as database objects

· Github Link

VibeZone Java Spark,Postgres,Handlebars

Website 2022

A collaborative project to create a website using java spark and the mustache handlebars templating language. The site was to provide a
platform where artists can set up profiles to advertise their music and upcoming musical events.

Github Link

Github Search Angular Typescript, Rxjs

Angular Application

- · An angular app that consumes the github api and users rxjs observables to display necessary user data. The app uses a github styles theme
- Github Link
- Site: Github Pages

OOPS , DSA and CNN

Java, C++, Python

DATA STRUCTURES AND ALGORITHMS

2022

- A repository with my various implementations of data structures and algoritms
- The repo also includes a python supervised learning project for gender detection using opency and numpy
- Github Link

Quotes AppAngular Typescript

ANGULAR APP 202.

- An angular application that allows user to add, delete, upvote, downvote quotes
- Github Link
- Site: Netlify Link

Work Experience __

Upwork, Fivver Online

Freelance Developer 2021 - Present

• Gained work experience working as a freelance software developer on remote jobs

Extracurricular Activity

CIT Club(Computing and Information Technology Club)

Kenya

TECHNICAL LEAD SEPT. 2021 - PRESENT

- · Gained expertise in mentorship from alumni and from bootcamps organised by the club.
- Currently participating as a Java technical lead teaching SpringBoot and android Concepts to members

Angular Kenya Kenya Kenya

Member Jun. 2022 - PRESENT

- · Gained experience listening to industry experts give talks on various fields especially on front-end development
- · Won angular Kenya merchandise in a debugging contest

Referees

Donata Akinyi Nairobi, Kenya

FRONT-END ENGINEER Carepay International

• Email: Akinyidonattah@gmail.com

Future Interests

Languages Haskell, Clojure, Python, Go, Rust

Feilds Deep learning and Neural networks, KMM, Rust System development, Functional Programming